







Summary

Jump to Section

Result-oriented professional with over 16 years of experience in IT Infrastructure Management, Application Management, Project Management, Service Management, Client Management, SLA Management and Technology Management. Strong experience in designing workflows using MS Visio and in ticketing tools like ServiceNow, Remedy and Release Management tools like JIRA

Work Experience

Tata Consultancy Services as Operations Manager Jan 2008 to Till Date

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Previous roles in Tata Consultancy Services include: Project Manager Solution Architect(Presales) Cross Functional Lead ITSMLead Change & Release Management Manager and Consultant Major Incident Manager

- Barclays Capital as Change Analyst Jan 2007 to Nov 2007
- Wipro Technologies as Project Engineer Mar 2005 to Dec 2006

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from DR. C V RAMAN UNIVERSITY in 2014

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Professional Cloud Service Manager ITIL4 Foundation Prince2 Practitioner Cloud Computing Foundation SIAM Professional

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
MS Visio, ServiceNow, JIRA, Remedy		15 Year(s)
SERVICE MANAGEMENT, Project Management		16 Year(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Kannada	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.